zapbi.com 2019-04-20

# ZAP Privacy Policy

##### **_LAST UPDATED ON: JANUARY, 29 2019_**

The ZAP group of companies ( **we, us, our** ) provide a web-application as a hosted cloud service to assist businesses in the areas of business intelligence, data management, data warehousing, reporting and analytics.

We understand the importance of, and are committed to, protecting your personal information.  This Privacy Policy explains how we manage your personal information (that is, information or an opinion about you, whether true or not, which identifies you or from which your identity is reasonably identifiable), including our obligations and your rights in respect of our dealings with your personal information.

Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy as it describes what happens to your personal information that is collected via our website at https:///www.zapbi.com (our **Website** ), and in the course of providing our services to you.

This Privacy Policy is our general privacy policy, but additional privacy terms may apply, to deal with relevant laws in your jurisdiction ( **Jurisdiction Specific Terms** ). To the extent that they might differ from this Privacy Policy, the Jurisdiction Specific Terms for your jurisdiction will override the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**How we collect your personal information**

We will collect and hold your personal information in a fair and lawful manner, and not in an intrusive way.  Where it is reasonably practical to do so, we will collect your personal information directly from you.  We may collect the personal information you directly give us through some of the following means:

  * when you make an inquiry, or use or register for our products and services (free or paid), or purchase and license our products through our Website;
  * in administering and performing any contracts with service providers;
  * when you contact us via telephone or email;
  * from correspondence (whether in writing or electronically);
  * through any mobile applications provided by our organisation;
  * while conducting customer satisfaction and market research surveys;
  * when administering any of our services; and
  * as otherwise required to manage our business.

You can also log in to our site using sign-in services such as Azure Active Directory. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.

However, in certain cases we may collect personal information from publicly available sources and third parties, such as suppliers, recruitment agencies, contractors, our clients and business partners.

If we collect personal information about you from a third party we will, where appropriate, request that the third party inform you that we are holding such information, how we will use and disclose it, and that you may contact us to gain access to and correct and update the information.

**Types of personal information we collect  **

The type of personal information we may collect can include (but is not limited to), your name, postal address, email address, phone numbers, billing information and, if applicable, employment information.

Where you do not wish to provide us with your personal information, we may not be able to provide you with requested services.

**Our purposes for handling your personal information**

As a general rule, we only process personal information for purposes that would be considered relevant and reasonable in the circumstances.

We collect, hold, use and disclose personal information to:

  * offer and provide you with our products and services;
  * manage and administer those products and services, including account keeping procedures;
  * communicate with you, including (but not limited to), emailing you tax invoices, dispatch and tracking information, returns and exchange authorisations;
  * comply with our legal and regulatory obligations; and
  * otherwise to manage our business.

We will not use or disclose your personal information for any other purpose unless you have consented to that use or disclosure.

We may disclose personal information between our organisations or to third parties such as our suppliers, organisations that provide us with technical and support services, or our professional advisers, where permitted by law.  If we disclose information to a third party, we generally require that the third party protect your information to the same extent that we do.

**Protection of personal information**

We will hold personal information as either secure physical records, electronically on our intranet system, in cloud storage, and in some cases, records on third party servers, which may be located overseas.

We maintain appropriate physical, procedural and technical security for our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, or modification of personal information.  This also applies to disposal of personal information.

We further protect personal information by restricting access to personal information to only those who need access to the personal information do their job.  Physical, electronic and managerial procedures have been employed to safeguard the security and integrity of your personal information.

For more information about the range of policies in place to provide a robust security environment, please visit our [Cloud security](https://www.zapbi.com/zap-cloud-security/) page. We ensure the on-going adequacy of these measures by regularly reviewing them.

We will destroy or de-identify personal information once it is no longer needed for a valid purpose or required to be kept by law.

If we experience a security breach where your personal information is lost, stolen, accessed, used, disclosed, copied, modified or disposed of by any unauthorized person or in an unauthorized manner, we will notify you as soon as reasonably possible. If you reasonably believe that there has been unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer.

**Direct Marketing**

Like most businesses, marketing is important to our continued success.  We believe we have a unique range of products and services that we provide to customers at a high standard.  We therefore like to stay in touch with customers and let them know about new opportunities.  If you have opted to receive such emails may provide you with information about new products, services and promotions either from us,

You can, at any time, opt out of receiving marketing material by contacting us. If you are a customer, you agree and acknowledge that even if you opt out of receiving marketing material, we will still send you essential information that we are legally required to send you relating to the services we provide. Once you opt out of receiving marketing material from us, you agree and acknowledge that this removal from our distribution lists may take several business days after the date of your request to be removed.

In order to deliver our products and services to you, we may disclose personal information to other organisations to whom we outsource certain functions including bulk mailing and market research, but only in relation to providing our products and services to you. We take reasonable steps to ensure that these organisations are bound by privacy obligations in relation to the protection of your personal information.

We take our obligations to protect personal information very seriously and we make every effort to deal only with parties who share and demonstrate the same attitude.

We will not disclose your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.

You may opt out at any time if you no longer wish to receive commercial messages from us.  You can make this request by contacting our Privacy Officer, or by using the unsubscribe function included in each marketing email.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file stored in your computer’s memory or on your hard disk for a pre-defined period of time.  We use cookies to identify specific machines in order to collect aggregate information on how visitors are experiencing the Website.  This information will help to better adapt the Website to suit personal requirements.  While cookies allow a computer to be identified, they do not permit any reference to a specific individual.  For more information on cookies, please visit our [Cookie Notice](https://www.zapbi.com/cookie-notice/).

**Accessing and correcting your personal information**

You may contact our Privacy Officer to request access to the personal information that we hold about you and/or to make corrections to that information, at any time.  On the rare occasions when we refuse access, we will provide you with a written notice stating our reasons for refusing access.  We may seek to recover from you reasonable costs incurred for providing you with access to any of the personal information about you held by us.

We are not obliged to correct any of your personal information if it does not agree that it requires correction and may refuse to do so.  If we refuse a correction request, we will provide you with a written notice stating our reasons for refusing.

We will respond to all requests for access to or correction of personal information within a reasonable time.

**Inter-jurisdictional  transfers of personal information**

The related bodies corporate that make up the ZAP group of companies may share personal information with each other, where permitted by law.

**ZAP Entity** | **Regions Covered** | **Address**  
---|---|---  
Zap Technology Pty Ltd. | Asia Pacific | 854 Lorimer Street 

Port Melbourne 3207 VIC.

Australia  
  
Zap Technology Limited | Europe, Middle-East and Africa | 33 Cavendish Square 

London W1G 0PW

United Kingdom  
  
ZAP Technology LLC | Americas  | 8875 Hidden River Parkway 

Suite 300

Tampa, FL 33637

United States of America  
  
From time to time we may also engage an overseas recipient to provide cloud-based storage services to us.  Please note that the use of overseas service providers to store personal information will not always involve a disclosure of personal information to that overseas provider.

We may disclose your personal information to the following service providers:

**Service Provider** | **Application** | **Location**  
---|---|---  
Microsoft Azure | Cloud provider hosting Customer Data 

User authentication

Logging and reporting

Only used by ZAP SaaS

| Customer data is hosted at the customer’s elected location, as set forth in our Terms of Service.  
Microsoft Dynamics 365 | Customer Relationship Management 

Service license provider

| United States  
HubSpot | Cloud-based CRM and Marketing service | United States  
Zendesk | Cloud-based Service Provider 

ZAP Customer HelpDesk

| United States  
SendGrid | Cloud-based email provider 

Only used by ZAP SaaS

| United States  
  
As at the date of this Privacy Policy, we are not likely to disclose personal information to other recipients outside of your jurisdiction, unless you direct us to send your information to a particular overseas recipient.  The countries in which the overseas recipients will be located will be the countries nominated by you in accordance with your request.  If in future we do propose to disclose personal information overseas, we will, where practicable, advise you of the countries in which any overseas recipients are likely to be located.

By providing your personal information to us, you consent to us disclosing your personal information to any such overseas recipients for purposes necessary or useful in the course of operating our business.

If you do not want us to disclose your information to overseas recipients, please let us know.

**Resolving personal information concerns**

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about this Privacy Policy, or how we handle your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer:

**The Privacy Officer**  
ZAP Technology Pty Ltd.  
854 Lorimer Street, Port Melbourne 3207 VIC. Australia

Email: [privacy@zapbi.com](mailto:privacy@zapbi.com)

We take all complaints seriously, and will respond to your complaint within a reasonable period.

**TAKE DOWN NOTICES**

Although we reserve the right to screen or monitor content on our systems, we generally do not do so. If you discover content that you believe should be taken down, you may file a complaint.

Your take down request must include specific information about the allegedly offending content. If your complaint is about copyright, trademark, or publicity rights infringement you must be the copyright owner.

Upon receiving a request:

  * If the complaint claims infringement of copyright, we will promptly remove the content while we evaluate the complaint.
  * If the complaint claims (1) infringement of trademark, privacy, or publicity rights, or (2) that the content is obscene, child pornography, or depicts the exploitation of children, we may, in our discretion, remove the content.
  * If the complaint makes some other claim, we may, in our discretion, take down the content while the complaint is evaluated. However our default position will be to not take down content while we evaluate the complaint.
  * If we do take down content, we’ll notify the user who posted it.

Where contacting us, you have the option to remain anonymous or use a pseudonym. However, this right will not apply if it is impracticable for us to communicate with you that way or where we are required or authorised by law to only deal with individuals who have identified themselves.

Questions, requests or complaints should be made in writing by email at privacy@zapbi.com.

**Consent**

By your use of our website and our products or services, you consent to the collection, use, storage, disclosure and management of your personal information in accordance with the Policy and as otherwise permitted by the Regulations.

**Changes**

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time, and we will strive to notify you of such changes.

The last update to this document was: **29 January 2019.**

**Jurisdiction-specific terms**

**Australia**

The ZAP group entity for Australia is Zap Technology Pty Ltd.

As an Australian company we are bound by the Australia Privacy Principles ( **APPs** ) in the _Privacy Act 1988_ (Cth) ( **Privacy Act** ).

In addition to the terms of the Privacy Policy, please note that:

  * **Overseas transfers of personal information**

By providing your personal information to us, you consent to us disclosing your personal information recipients outside of Australia as set out in our Privacy Policy, and agree that APP 8.1 will not apply to such disclosures.  For the avoidance of doubt, in the event that an overseas recipient breaches the APPs, that entity will not be bound by, and you will not be able seek redress under, the Privacy Act.

  * **Office of the Australian Information Commissioner**

If you are dissatisfied with the handling of your complaint, you may contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner:

**Office of the Australian Information Commissioner**

Address: GPO Box 5218. Sydney  NSW  2001

Telephone: 1300 363 992

Email: enquiries@oaic.gov.au
